氦
Helium.
- 对了  - 是吧
- Yes.  - Yes.
这是Taylor Swift
Taylor Swift.
没错
Yes.
圆周率
Pi.
对了
Yes.
她姓卡戴珊
Kardashian.
叫什么?
More specific.
科勒?
Khloe?
对了!
Yes!
看吧 我记住了
See, I remembered
因为我发现 长得像金的 就是金
because if it looks like Kim it's Kim,
如果长得有点像金 那就是考特妮
if it looks kind of like Kim it's Kourtney,
如果长得完全不像金 那就是科勒
and if it looks nothing like Kim it's Khloe.
好吧
Oh.
哦
Oh,
这是文氏图解 我记得是因为
that's a Venn Diagram, and I remember because
我一直在想
I thought to myself,
"他什么时候能别再说这个图了?"
"Venn is he gonna stop talking about this diagram?"
"文氏"与英语中"什么时候"谐音
- 你们干嘛呢?  - 这个嘛
- What are you guys doing?  - Oh, well,
我们决定利用早餐的时间
we decided to use our breakfast time
帮助对方 扩大自己的领域的知识面
to expand our respective knowledge bases.
让我试试
Oh, let me try.
好啊
Okay.
呃 氢原子 Maroon 5的Adam 跪安吧
Hmm, atom of hydrogen, Adam of Maroon 5, mic drop.
魔力红是美国摇滚乐队 Adam为歌手之一
那个 谁是跪安?
I'm sorry, who is Mike Drop?
对了 Penny 你一会能不能和我一起
Oh, hey, Penny, do you want to go to the airport
去机场接我妈妈?
with me later to pick up my mother?
- 好啊  - 谢了
- Sure.  - Thanks.
- 没什么  - 还有 Penny
- No problem.  - Hey, Penny,
那个 反正你也要去机场
um, since you're already gonna be at the airport,
那我还用去吗?
do I need to go?
你为什么不想去机场接你妈妈?
Why don't you want to get your mother from the airport?
如果她不会一路上整整四十分钟都在
Well, I can do without the 40-minute car ride
全方位地吐槽我的话 其实我也挺想去接她的
where she criticizes every aspect of my life.
四十分钟就够她吐槽你的了?
She can cover it in a car ride?
你的站姿就够我吐槽四十分钟的
I could do 40 minutes on your posture alone.
你真的想让我
You really want me to pick up
一个人去接你妈妈?
your mother all by myself?
我是觉得
Hmm, I just feel like
你们正好可以借此增进感情
it would be a good chance for you to bond.
还是你可以借此避免和她接触?
Or a way for you to avoid her?
我不知道他在卡片上写了什么
I don't know what he's putting on those cards,
但是你真的比以前聪明了
but you are smarter than ever.
好吧 你要是真的不想去 我去接就好了
Fine, if you really want me to, I will pick your mom up.
真的?
Seriously?
是啊 她是我婆婆嘛
Yeah, you know what, she is my mother-in-law,
我也希望我们能和谐相处
and I'd like for us to have a good relationship.
你真的好成熟啊
That is very mature of you,
而我就可以继续怂下去了
so I'm gonna go ahead and say, "Suckah."
- 好了 继续学习吧  - 好
- All right, back to learning.  - Okay.
这个简单 这是教科学的比尔
Oh, easy, Bill Nye the Science Guy.
"比尔教科学"是美国一档科教节目
不过我把他称为...
Or as I know him...
"'与星共舞'里的怪老头"
"Creepy old dude from Dancing with the Stars."
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state  *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait!  *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool  *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools  *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids  *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery  *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang  *
生活大爆炸 第九季第23集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥放假了
校对: UUUUUU放假不放假有区别吗
翻译: 凤梨酥 小黄小可爱 李小宝Licht
翻译: 無限月讀 钥匙君 舒大卷子
你们知不知道有一场复仇者电影的放映会?
Did you guys see there's an Avengers screening?
Joss Whedon会在现场展示一些被删减的片段
Joss Whedon's gonna show some deleted scenes
还有问答环节
and do a question and answer session.
我倒真有几个关于上一部复仇者电影的问题
Oh, well, I have a few questions for him
想要问他... 当然我已经有很多答案了
about the last Avengers movie... and a whole lot of answers.
什么时候放映?
When's the screening?
就在今晚 不过座位是先到先得的
Uh, it's tonight, but it's first-come, first-served,
所以我们应该早点去排队
so we should probably get there early and wait in line.
好啊
Let's do it.
Penny在陪我妈呢 加我一个
Penny's busy with my mother, so I'm in.
哦 不好意思啊
Oh, bad news.
Amy逼我陪她去逛街
Amy's making me go shopping with her later,
所以我们都去不了了
so looks like none of us can go.
我们又不是没有你就不能出去玩了
You do realize we're allowed to have fun without you?
其实没有你我们才能玩的开心
In fact, that's usually the trick to it.
我们得什么时候到?
What time do we need to get there?
呃 大概三点钟吧
Uh, I'd say by 3:00.
你们真的要抛下我去吗?
You're really going without me?
这又没什么的
It's not a big deal.
你去陪Amy逛街
Go shopping with Amy,
我们会帮你留一个位子的
and we'll save a spot in line for you.
你又没有权利给任何人留位子
You don't have the authority to save places in the line.
如果我这样做的话 我就是插队了
If I do that, I'll be cutting.
大家都这么做的
People do it all the time.
排队的黄金法则就是
You know the golden rule of line etiquette:
"乱插队的没屁眼"
"No cuts, no buts, no coconuts."
如果你那么在乎这件事的话
If you really care that much,
你可以下一个手机软件 雇人帮你干事
there are apps now that'll let you hire people to do stuff
比如买菜排队什么的
like errands and wait in lines.
还真的有人工作就是去排队?
People are actually waiting in lines as a job?
听到这种事我自我感觉好多了
Boy, makes me feel better about my life.
有些人一个小时就能赚20美元呢
Some of these guys make over $20 an hour.
这下子我感觉又不好了
And now I feel worse again.
我早就预料到Leonard会不来接我的
I'm not surprised Leonard chose to avoid picking me up.
他一辈子都不习惯亲密关系
He's battled intimacy issues his whole life.
他持续勃起有困难吗?
Does he have difficulty maintaining erections?
哇
Wow.
连停车场都还没开出去呢
Didn't even make it out of the parking lot.
呃 要不我们别聊Leonard了
Uh, you know what, enough about Leonard.
我们聊聊你吧
Let's talk about you.
你这几天在这里想干什么?
What would you like to do while you're here?
亲爱的 我是精神病医生
Dear, I'm a psychiatrist.
你不需要避免和我进行亲密的交谈的
You don't have to avoid having intimate conversations with me.
我其实是希望我们能亲密一些的
Well, I'd actually like for us to be close,
但是我们能不能从最喜欢看的书开始聊起
but maybe we start with our favorite books
最后再讨论我丈夫的性器官
and work our way up to my husband's sex organs.
可以啊
Very well.
你最近看什么书呢?
What's the last book you read?
家居杂志
呃 陶器室春季特刊算吗?
Um, does Pottery Barn, Spring count?
Penny 你希望你的婆婆喜欢你 这是很自然的心理
Penny, it's only natural to want your mother-in-law to like you,
我知道有时候我让人害怕
and I acknowledge I can be an intimidating person.
我要怎么样才能让你轻松一点呢?
So what can I do to make this process easier for you?
呃 你能不能
Uh, for starters,
不要用心理学分析我说的每一句话?
maybe you can not psychoanalyze everything I say?
那我用心理学分析你说的话的时候
And how does it make you feel
你是什么感受呢?
when I psychoanalyze everything you say?
非常不舒服
Uncomfortable.
我开玩笑呢 亲爱的
That was a joke, dear.
哦 对不起
Oh. Sorry.
没想到你还会开玩笑
Didn't know you made those.
嘿 要不我们婆媳俩今天晚上
Hey, listen, what if we have a little
一起吃一顿晚饭吧?
mother-in-law-daughter-in-law dinner tonight?
就我们两个人吗?
So just the two of us?
要不我再请几个朋友来吧
Or I invite a few girlfriends,
刚刚你说"就我们两个人"的时候
'cause hearing you say "the two of us"
我突然就寒毛直竖了
just sent a chill right down my spine.
嘿
Hey.
你来干什么?
What are you doing here?
你又不是Sheldon
You're not Sheldon.
我就知道你会问这个问题
I thought that might come up.
Sheldon雇我陪你去逛街
Sheldon hired me to go shopping with you.
等等
Hold on.
他付钱给你就为了不和我一起出门?
He paid you to get out of spending time with me?
也不是这样啦
No, it's not like that.
他是需要去排个队
There's a long line he'd rather stand in.
那我们去干什么呢? 买衣服还是买玩具?
So what are we doing? Old Navy, Build-A-Bear?
我反正都能拿钱
I get paid either way.
我不会陪你去逛街的
We're not going shopping together.
你确定吗? 我能帮你提包啊
You sure? I'm happy to hold your bag.
Sheldon还给我了一点钱让我去买热狗香肠呢
And Sheldon gave me money for a hotdog on a stick.
你知道我现在为什么不高兴吗?
Can you understand why I might be annoyed right now?
小姐 我只是来干活的
Look, lady, I just work here.
我们一起排过很多队 是吧?
We've waited in a lot of lines together, haven't we?
还记得我们参加的那次
Remember when we camped out
动漫大会上的神秘博士主题露营吗?
for the Doctor Who panel at Comic-Con?
是啊 和其他粉丝一起睡在星空下
Yeah, sleeping under the stars with other fans
分享着我们共同热爱的东西
who love the show as much as we do.
醒过来之后想着到底是谁偷了我们的钱包
Waking up, wondering which one of those fans stole our wallets.
Stuart 你在这里干什么?
Stuart, what are you doing here?
Sheldon 你真是我这辈子见过的
Sheldon, you are the most inconsiderate person
最无良的人了!
I have ever met in my entire life!
你怎么能通过打发我过去
Where do you get off sending me
来逃避和你女朋友的约会呢?
to shop with your girlfriend?!
我不明白你的意思
I don't understand.
我之前雇你的时候你可是很开心的
You were happy to do this when I hired you.
为什么... 为什么现在反倒对我有意见了?
Why... why are you upset with me now?
噢 我没有意见 但是Amy现在大发雷霆
Oh, I'm not upset with you, but Amy's pretty bent out of shape,
所以她雇我让你尝尝这种滋味
so she hired me to let you have it.
好吧 礼尚往来 很公平
Well, I suppose turnabout is fair play.
公你妹的平啊 你个自私的混蛋!
You're darn right it's fair play, you selfish jerk!
你知道吗 每当我以为
You know, just when I think
我们的关系有所进展的时候
we're making progress in our relationship,
我们又回到了老样子
we revert to our old patterns
任何想法和感受都难以言表
where thoughts and feelings go unexpressed.
我想说 如果他不愿意和我一起去购物
I mean, if he didn't want to go shopping with me,
为什么不直接说出来呢?
why didn't he just say so?
说不定他插不上嘴
Maybe he couldn't get a word in edgewise.
抱歉 我一直说个不停
I'm sorry, I've been going on and on.
没关系 亲爱的
Oh, it's all right, dear.
Sheldon的思维不但机智还很复杂
Sheldon has a brilliant and complicated mind.
和他发展一段男女关系很艰难
It's understandable that being in a relationship with him
是可以理解的
could be trying.
有一次我叫他"宝贝儿"
I called him "babe" once.
他问我是不是磕药了
He asked me to get a drug test.
我欣赏你的决心
Well, I do admire your resolve.
你是一个了不起的女人 谢谢你
You're an extraordinary woman. Thank you.
你知道 她是我的婆婆
You know, she's my mother-in-law.
为什么我不能和她这么和谐呢?
Why can't I bond with her like that?
她把Sheldon当亲生儿子看待
Amy's with Sheldon who she loves like a son.
你虽然和他儿子在一起
You're with her son...
但她没那么上心
who she doesn't.
你能想象我用了五年时间才让他帮我按摩按摩吗?
Do you realize it took me five years to get a massage from him?
Sheldon能这么做已经跨出一大步了
Oh, well, that still could be a big step for Sheldon.
三分钟
Three minutes.
他还用了厨房计时器
And he used a kitchen timer.
我感觉自己就像一个半熟的鸡蛋
I felt like a soft-boiled egg.
知道吗 和Leonard在一起
You know, being in a relationship with Leonard
也是有很多挑战的
also comes with its challenges.
是的
Yes.
不过 有什么办法呢?
Well, what can you do?
说不定是Sheldon来道歉的
Maybe it's Sheldon, here to say he's sorry.
Sheldon说他很抱歉
Sheldon says he's sorry.
Bernadette 我给你五块钱把门砸上
Bernadette, I'll give you five dollars to slam the door.
我只要三块钱就行了
I would have done it for three.
天哪 一直在这儿站着真累人
Boy, all this standing's making me tired.
还好我带了折叠拐杖椅
Good thing I brought my collapsible stick chair.
别提折叠拐杖椅了
Not the stick chair.
你坐在上面就像个傻子
You look like an idiot on that thing.
棍子和石头会让我骨折
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
但是棍子上的小椅子可是很舒服的哦
but chairs on sticks are comfy.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
和Amy一切顺利吗?
Is everything smoothed out with Amy?
不 她还是很生气
Uh, no, she's still pretty mad.
你有向我一样真诚地道歉了吗?
Did you make the apology as sincere as I would have?
我说了"Sheldon说他很抱歉"
I said, "Sheldon says he's sorry."
你这么说又有点夸张了
Oh, well, that's laying it on a little thick.
你觉得是时候你自己去和她道歉了吗?
You think it's time you apologize to her yourself?
我想是吧
I suppose so.
但如果我现在走了的话 我就拿不到位子了
But if I get out of the line, I'll lose my spot.
我很乐意在你回来之前帮你占位
I'm happy to hold your place till you get back.
你愿意吗?
You would do that?
考虑到这样我就能从你这里赚更多的钱 是的
Consider it my way of getting more of your money.
你真是个好人
You're a good man.
Beverly 你知道Penny
So, Beverly, did you know Penny
是我们制药公司
is the number three sales rep
排行前三的销售代表吗?
at our pharmaceutical company?
哦 我不知道你们在一起工作
Oh, I didn't realize you two work together.
呃 严格来说不是的
Well, we don't exactly.
我是研究组的微生物学家
I'm a microbiologist for the research team.
那你现在研究什么呢
Oh, what are you currently developing?
一些新型的抗焦虑药
Some exciting new anti-anxiety drugs.
很有意思
That's interesting.
我刚参加了一个关于儿童焦虑的讲座
I just attended a lecture on pediatric anxiety.
是雅诺斯基博士的讲座吗?
Oh, was it, uh, Dr. Jenofski?
我刚看了他的TED讲话!
I just saw his TED Talk!
就是他
It was.
还是说说Penny吧
Let's get back to Penny.
你不是刚要告诉我
Hey, weren't you telling me
你公司配车的事情吗?
something great about your company car?
呃..
Um...
车上配有座位供暖
It has seat warmers.
Amy! 开门 Amy!
Amy! Amy!
- 开门 Amy!  - 进来
- Amy!  - Come in.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
Beverly 见到你真好!
Oh, Beverly, good to see you!
很想跟你聊聊 可我还要排队
I'd love to chat, but there's a line
队伍马上就要开始向前移动了 所以就这么着吧
that could start moving any minute, so let's do this.
Amy?听我说
Amy?
恰当的道歉有三个步骤
A proper apology requires three steps.
第一步 认错
Step one-- an admission of wrong doing.
Amy 我错了 第二步...
Amy, I was wrong. Step two...
承诺不再犯错
a promise never to repeat said action.
Amy 我不会再那么干了 我承诺
Amy, that action will never be repeated, and that's a promise.
第三步... 诚恳的请求原谅
Step three... an earnest request for forgiveness.
Amy 我希望你能原谅我
Amy, I hope you can forgive me.
而且希望你现在就能原谅我
And I hope you do it right now,
因为下面还有车等着我呢
'cause there's an Uber waiting downstairs,
而且我也不想跟我的司机Ganesh
and I don't want to repeat this apology nonsense
再道歉一次
with my driver Ganesh.
好吧
Fine.
谢谢! 你真善解人意!
Oh, thanks! You're a peach!
Beverly 我们以后再聊
Beverly, we'll catch up soon.
Bernadette 很高兴见到你
Bernadette, it was a pleasure as always,
Penny 你牙齿上有根菠菜
Penny, you have spinach in your teeth.
我牙齿上那个菠菜有多长时间了?
How long have I had spinach in my teeth?
机场见到你的时候就有
Since the airport, dear.
你看起来像身后长了根支架
You look like you come with a kickstand.
你没法让我觉得不舒服
You can't make me feel bad.
也许不能 Leonard你上
Hmm, maybe not. Leonard?
外星人把你送回来的时候
So, when the aliens brought you back,
忘了把探测器取出来?
they just left the probe in?
我回来了
I'm back.
- 怎么样了?  - 挺好的
- Hey, how'd it go?  - It went well.
我发现如果你从来不道歉
Yeah, I've learned that if you never say you're sorry,
你真道歉的时候会让他们很不自在
the times you do really puts them on their heels.
Stuart 你现在可以走了
Uh, Stuart, I relieve you of your line duties.
我走之前还有谁有什么事情吗?
Anyone else need anything before I go?
如果能取笑一下Raj我就给你一块钱
I'll give you a dollar if make fun of Raj.
- 太小气了  - 那五块
- That's mean.  - Five.
如果老虎看起来像傻子 那你就看起来像老虎
You look like Tigger if Tigger looked like a jackass.
如果你需要有人写推荐信
Uh, if you ever need a reference or anything,
我很愿意帮忙
just let me know.
大家好
Hey, guys.
你来了
You made it.
你看见了吗?
Did you see that?
他刚插队了
He just cut the line.
他和朋友一起呢 没事的
He's just joining his friends; it's fine.
不行 这是不对的
No, it's not fine.
这违反了排队的原则
It is a breach of line etiquette.
我们排在队伍前面
We're near the front of the line.
怎么着都进得去
We'll get in either way.
如果我们前面的每个人都让人插队会怎么样?
What if every person in front of us lets someone cut?
我们还是进得去
We'd still get in.
如果插队的那些人再让人插队会怎么样?
What if each of those people let someone cut?
还是进得去
Still get in.
如果那些新插进来的人继续让人插队呢?
But then each of those people let someone cut?
还是进得去 不过进去之前
We'd still get in, but first I'd hit you
我会先用他的折凳敲你脑袋
over the head with his stick chair.
- 请听我说  - 别啊
- Excuse me.  - Oh, please don't.
呃 我一不小心就
Uh, uh, I couldn't help but notice
看到你插队了
that you cut the line.
我是跟我朋友一起的
Oh, uh, I'm with my friends.
不用你操心
It's cool.
不行
Well, no.
我必须要操心
It's not cool.
如果座位都是需要提前预约的
If there were reserved seating,
而且我们都有票的话 那就没事
and we all had tickets, that would be fine.
但是这是先到先得的
But this line is first-come, first-served.
而不是"晚到先得"
Not "show up tardy and nevertheless be first served".
来 击个掌
Right here.
不要
No.
你必须要排到后面去
You need to go to the back of the line.
谁说你是队伍管理员了?
Uh, who made you line monitor?
四年级的时候 Wunch女士钦点的我
Mrs. Wunch in fourth grade.
我的宣言是"只要是笔直的队伍
And my slogan was "a line that's straight
就是好队伍"
is a line that's great"
这货是在认真的?
Is this guy for real?
我多想说不是的
Boy, I wish I could say no.
Sheldon能道歉还是很不错的
That was very nice of Sheldon to apologize.
是的 他是变了很多
Well, he's come a long way.
或许花很久时间变了很少
Or a short way very slowly,
所以感觉是变了很多
so it feels like a long way.
你俩的关系真是太好了
Your relationship with him is fascinating.
我正在准备写一本高质量情侣的书
I'm preparing to write a book on high-achieving couples,
我想对你俩做个访谈
and I would love to interview the both of you.
可以啊
Oh, sure.
我会... 我会跟Sheldon说这事儿的
I'll... I'll talk to Sheldon about it.
你知不知道Bernadette的老公原来是宇航员
You know, Bernadette's husband is a former astronaut.
真的?
Really?
你觉得他愿不愿意
Do you think he would be interested
一起来做访谈?
in being interviewed as well?
我还需要问他愿不愿意?
Do I think he'd be interested?
有时候他在洗澡的时候
Sometimes I hear him pretending to be interviewed
我就听见他在假装被访谈呢
when he's alone in the bathroom.
完美!
Wonderful!
我会给你联系方式的
I'll give you my contact information.
呃 你应该也问问Penny
Um, you should probably talk to Penny, too.
问她啥?
About what?
够了 你知道不?
Okay, you know what?
这太傻了
This is ridiculous.
我一整天都在想着
I've been trying to make
能和你的关系更进一步
a connection with you all day,
很明显 没有什么用
and clearly I'm getting nowhere.
你是想要一种关系
Well, are you seeking a connection
还是仅仅就是认可?
or just some form of validation?
我想要的是一种友谊
What I was seeking was some sort of friendship.
但是现在 你不羞辱我就行了
But at this point, I'll take you not insulting me to my face.
我从来没想过羞辱你啊
My intention was never to insult you.
但是你整天都在!
You've been doing it all day!
你到底知不知道什么叫做羞辱?!
Do you even know what an insult is?!
显然它不是个医学术语
Well, it's not a clinical term.
但是一个例子就是你嫁给了我的儿子
But one example would be your marrying my son,
但是却没有邀请我去婚礼 甚至都没有告诉我
and not inviting me or even telling me
你们都要办婚礼了
the wedding was taking place.
好吧 好例子
Okay, good example.
那你觉得Joss Whedon会让破坏规矩和插队的人
What about Joss Whedon's work makes you think he'd be okay
Joss Whedon为复仇者联盟系列导演编剧
来看他的作品吗?!
with rule-breakers and line-cutters?!
复仇者联盟本来就是打破规矩的人!
The Avengers are rule-breakers!
充满报复心理就是他们的职责!
Being vengeful is in their job description!
他们是为神盾局工作
They work for SHIELD,
神盾局是被美国政府所管辖的!
which is a sanctioned department of the U.S. Government!
你是在美国政府管辖的
Do you work for a sanctioned department
部门里工作吗?
of the U.S. Government?
事实上我就是
As a matter of fact I do.
一个小地方叫车管所
At a little place called the DMV.
他更胜一筹啊
He's got him there.
D甚至都代表了部门这个词
The D even stands for department.
不好意思大家!
Excuse me!
不好意思 我能
Excuse me, can I please
听听大家的意见吗?
see a show of hands?
谁很不爽这个人这里插队?
Who here takes issue with this person cutting the line?
看吧
Told you.
好吧 你们的行为让人真心寒!
Well, what a sad state of affairs!
你们全部都被生活打压的够够的
That you've all been so ground down
你们甚至没有注意到有人不尊重你们
by life, you don't even notice when someone disrespects you.
简直不能相信我们要被打
I can't believe we're gonna get beat up,
却不是因为你的凳子
and it's not because of your chair.
你们要知道 现在 在队伍的最后面
You know, right now, at the back of this line,
有一个同你们一样的影迷
there's a movie fan like you
不能入场了
who's not going to get in,
因为这个人不在乎
because this person simply doesn't care.
61年前
Yeah, well, 61 years ago,
也有一个人站在队伍后面
there was another person at the back of the line
她的名字是Rosa Parks
and her name was Rosa Parks.
Rosa Parks，美国50-60年代的黑人民权运动引导者。
你可能需要假装你是黑人
Okay, you may have to pretend you're black
来帮助我们离开这里
to get us out of here.
让我们追随这位勇敢女性的脚步
Now, let's follow in that brave woman's footsteps,
为我们自己站出来
and stand up for ourselves!
我知道她是为了能够坐下而站起来抗争
And-and I realize that she stood up by remaining seated,
但现在不是欣赏这个对比的时候
but now is not that time to enjoy the irony of that.
我再问你们
Now, I ask you again.
有没有人反对这个人...?
Who here takes issue with this person...?
我们为什么要听你的? 你自己也插队了
Why should we listen to you? You cut the line yourself.
我几乎绝对没有
I most certainly did not.
我看到你了
I saw you.
如果你觉得头晕
If you're feeling dizzy,
因为风水轮流转
it's because the tables have turned.
抱歉 我付钱让人在这里帮我排队
Excuse me, I paid someone to wait in line for me,
我来的时候
and then when I arrived,
他走 所以你看到的 好女人
he left, so what you saw, my good woman,
是换位不是插队
was "swapsies", not "cutsies".
不 不 不 等等!
Oh, no, no, no, no, wait!
我再问一次 举手示意
I ask you all again. A show of hands.
有没有人反对...? 不要走了
Who here takes issue...? Well, stop moving!
他要进去了!
He's gonna get in!
- 让他去  - 我不能
- Buddy, let it go.  - No, I can't.
这是不对的
This isn't right.
你已经尽力了
You did everything you could.
不 我还可以
No, I could've done more.
现在你抹黑了
Now, now, you denigrated the memory
一位伟大的民众权利先锋
of a great civil rights pioneer.
大家都可以提问这个了
That's all anyone could ask.
说实话 我很惊讶你会在意这场婚礼
To be honest, I'm surprised you cared about the wedding at all.
我还是人啊 Penny
I'm still human, Penny.
自己儿子的婚礼没有被邀请
Not getting invited to my own son's wedding
很难忽略啊
is difficult to ignore.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel.
她没邀请任何人
She didn't invite any of us.
那就是一时冲动!
It was spur of the moment!
但我们可以在网上看到现场直播
But we did get to see a live stream of it on the Internet.
我可以在网上看到?
I could've watched it on the Internet?
谢谢你
Thank you.
那如果我们邀请你来维加斯
So if we would have asked you to come to Vegas
观礼 你会来吗?
to see us get married, you would've come?
不会 我会说你们正在犯一个大错
No, I would've said you're making a huge mistake.
但邀请是好的
But an invitation would've been nice.
你真的觉得我们做错了?
You really think we made a mistake?
那会儿我是这么想的
At the time I did.
但我从来没有看到Leonard这么高兴过
But I-I've never seen Leonard so happy,
所以... 也许是我错了
so... perhaps I was wrong.
哇哦
Wow.
好了
Okay.
这样如何?
Well, um, how about this?
趁你在城里
Maybe while you're still in town,
Leonard和我再举办一场小型仪式
Leonard and I could have another small ceremony.
如果你感兴趣的话
You know, if you're interested.
我觉得这是完全可以接受的
I would find that perfectly acceptable.
她觉得
She would find it
是完全可以接受的!
perfectly acceptable!
你们看到了吗? 我们好上了!
You guys saw it! We bonded!
Howie啊?
Howie?
你没事吧? 你在里面有一会儿了
You doing okay? You've been in there a while.
我很好 马上出来
I'm fine. Be right out.
我是一个美国英雄吗?
Am I an American hero?
这是一个好问题 Jim
Well, that's a good question, Jim.
你不觉得当一位宇航员离开这个星球
Don't you think once an astronaut leaves the planet,
他就是地球上所有国家的英雄吗?
he's a hero to all the nations of the Earth?
好的
Okey dokey.
我还有时间再回答一个提问
I think I have time for one more question.